(Penny:)Okay, it won't
be that bad.
(Penny:)We wouldn't even sit in
your spot while you're gone.
(Sheldon:)You're darn right, you wouldn't.
(Sheldon:)No matter where I am,
this will always be my spot.
(Sheldon:)Like an embassy
(Sheldon:)in a foreign country,
(Sheldon:)this seat is the sovereign
soil of my bottom.
(Leonard:)Just nod and smile.
He's almost gone.
(Amy:)Sheldon, what do you think?
(Sheldon:)Very well. I'm on board.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)I accept this
five-week mission
(Sheldon:)to share a living space
with my girlfriend.
(Amy:)Oh. This is so exciting.
(Sheldon:)Well, now, don't be surprised
if, like Star Trek,
it's canceled in three.
(Raj:)I have to say, I am happy
with your ob-gyn.
Cool. 'Cause she says
you're doing a great job as
"weird friend who doesn't have
to be at every appointment."
I'm the son of a gynecologist.
I could be helpful.
(Bernadette:)It would help
(Bernadette:)if you stopped telling me
I have a textbook cervix.
(Raj:)The polite response is,
"Thank you for noticing."